good morning people apparently the Hells
Angels own that brothel out there out on
80 we're doing a program to hand in your
gun for uh yeah handguns range that's
what the poster said yeah yeah wanted us
to sponsor that you know but up terror
said uh-huh
hey guys can I help you sir I would just
the lady out front said that maybe I
could talk to Trudy for a second the
lady up front was wrong sir we are in a
meeting she is working right now hi 25
seconds no sir hey what are you doing
how are you good I got you this kind of
person yeah can you turn around god I
was just wondering if you'd like to
maybe go grab a cup of coffee sometime
look - all right so I guess I'll I'll
call you or something okay what's your
number
you can just call Nathan wonder you can
just stop by here any time it would be
fine if you wanted to stop by at any
time or a great 32:32 inconvenient
it wasn't it inconvenient pullin Craig
pullin Craig pullin okay see you later -
yeah - a charge sitting in a tree shut
up you don't think it's cute you think
it's funny and you think it's pathetic
and you think it's sad Fu Fu and you
can everyone see this holy run it
through the computer pu l li m what
should we do no we have to get him stop
no no don't we can't do that we have
nothing we have no evidence oh my gosh
if we jump on him with no evidence Trudy
will say it's just cuz we're trying to
come / - find his home address find his
home address we need to get close to him
we need to find out what we can find out
I'm taking Trudy to Sears for a makeover
later and I will have some girl talk
time good and I will find out what she
knows about him the Google's the
sheriff's computer don't use Google
you've been looking up too much
pornography and you forgot how the
regular sheriff's computer works
[Music]